A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32 FA304
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
1925-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Harkness, Charles W.
Harkness, Anna M. Richardson
Commonwealth Fund
Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman
Harkness, Edward Stephen
FA304
13.7 Cubic Feet 32 boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Arrangement note
This series is arranged in four subseries:
Subseries 1: Alphabetical Files, 1925-1980
Subseries 2: Chemical Bank, 1971-1982
Subseries 3: Fiscal, 1981-1982
Subseries 4: Taxes
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
United States; War relief; Public health; Public welfare; Child welfare; Education, Rural; Hygiene; Law; New York (State); New York (N.Y.); Child mental health; Child psychology; Medicine, Rural; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Mental health; Legal issues; Legal research; Medical education; Medical research; Harkness, Charles W.; Phillips Exeter Academy; Harvard University; Harkness, Anna M. Richardson; Social Science Research Council; Yale University; Commonwealth Fund; Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman; Harkness, Edward Stephen; Columbia University
- Alphabetical Files, 1925-1980; 1
  - Alexander and Alexander, 1967-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander and Alexander, 1967-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alexander and Alexander, 1967-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Fund-Raising Counsel, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary Dinner (Union Club), October 24, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appropriations, 1959/1960-1976/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Appropriations, 1959/1960-1976/1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations, 1959/1960-1976/1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Appropriations, 1959/1960-1976/1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Audit, 1976/1977-1979/1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Audit, 1976/1977-1979/1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Audit Guide (Council on Foundations), 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bankers Trust Company, 1947-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Barabell Fund, 1930-1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted material.
  - Berry, George P., 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Birdsall, William E., 1943-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1958-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors - Journal Entries, 1919-1927 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Book Program - General, 1959-1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Book Program - General, 1959-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Book Program - Grant-in-Aid, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Book Program - Grant-in-Aid, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Book Program - Subsidies, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bowers, John Z., January-April, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bunnell, P. W., 1935-1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - By-Laws, 1919-1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - By-Laws, 1919-1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Change of Name Data, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Chapman, Carleton B., 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Chemical Bank, 1918-1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Chemical Bank, 1918-1965 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Chemical Bank, 1918-1965 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chemical Bank, 1966-1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Chemical Bank, 1966-1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Chemical Bank, 1966-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Chemical Bank, 1966-1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Childers, Ada, May 27, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Clemens Trust, 1940-1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Clemens Trust, 1940-1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Clemens Trust, 1940-1970 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Financial-Estimated Income, 1938-1946 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Incorporation, 1918-1952 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Division of Education (British Fellowships), 1935-1944 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - English Refugee Assistance Fund (Division of Education - Refugee Assistance Fund), 1940-1947 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1958-1980 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1958-1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Expense Accounts (Memoranda), 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Finance Committee - "Black Book" Policy, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Finance Committee - Reports for Board Meetings, 1946-1959 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Finance Committee - Reports for Board Meetings, 1946-1959 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Financial Statements, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Foundation Library Center, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Frye, Theodore R., March 4-14, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Galdston, Iago (Consultation), January 6-8, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Grants, Special (Policy), 1934-1946 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Harkness, Anna M., 1918-1945 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate), 1942-1951 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Estate), 1950-1957 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Estate-Escrow Agreement), 1951-1970 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Harkness House, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Haskins and Sells (Correspondence), 1921-1958 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Haskins and Sells (Correspondence), 1921-1958 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Haskins and Sells (Correspondence), 1921-1958 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Haskins and Sells (Correspondence), 1959-1977 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Haskins and Sells (Correspondence), 1959-1977 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Hilton Head Inn Meeting (May 5-9, 1971) - Foundation Executives Group Meeting, May-September, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Honoraria, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Income (Permanent Record), 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Income (Permanent Record), 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Insurance, 1949-1974 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Interface Program, 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Medical Activities (Special Research Grants), 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Medical Appropriations (Special Gifts), 1931-1947 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Medical Fellowships (Advanced), 1939-1947 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Medical Research (Appropriations), 1920-1959 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Medical Research (Appropriations), 1920-1959 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Mental Health (Appropriations), 1937-1957 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Mental Hygiene in England, 1937-1957 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Moore, William H., February-March, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - National Information Bureau, June 5-8, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Newton, Quigg, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1920-1942 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - New York City (Taxes), 1935-1951 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - New York State (Taxes), 1933-1969 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Company, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Plimpton, Calvin H., 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - President's Revolving Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - The Public Interest Institution as Investor (H. David Rosenbaum), July-October, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Division of Publications (Budgets), 1946-1959 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Division of Publications (Financial Statements/Memoranda), 1946-1959 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Division of Publications (Financial Statements/Memoranda), 1946-1959 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Division of Publications (Journal Entries/Ledger Accounts), 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Division of Publications (Statements), 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Puerto Rico (Annual Return of Organization Exempt from Income Tax), 1969-1978 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Refugee Assistance Fund (Division of Education - Mothers and Children Fund/English Refugee Assistance Fund), June-August, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    Related Archival Materials note
    Also see box 7, folder 46.
  - Rogers and Butler, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Sage, Gray, Todd and Sims, 1941-1957 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Sanazaro, Paul J., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (Questionnaire - 1970), February-March, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (Special Study of Security Markets), 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (Special Study of Security Markets), 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Somers, Anne, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - South Bronx Open Space Task Force, Inc., October-November, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 120)
- Chemical Bank, 1971-1982; 2
  - Investment Account, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Investment Account, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Investment Account, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Investment Account, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Investment Account, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Investment Account, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Investment Account, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Investment Account, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Investment Account, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Investment Account, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Investment Account, June 1982 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - Investment Account (30-70057), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - Investment Account (30-70057), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Investment Account (30-70057), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - Investment Account (30-70057), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Investment Account (30-70057), April-May, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 146)
  - Investment Account (30-75306), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - Investment Account (30-75306), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Investment Account (30-75306), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Investment Account (30-75308), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Investment Account (30-75308), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Investment Account (30-75308), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Investment Account (30-75309), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 153)
  - Investment Account (30-75309), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 154)
  - Investment Account (30-75309), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 155)
  - Investment Account (30-75310), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 156)
  - Investment Account (30-75310), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 157)
  - Investment Account (30-75310), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - Investment Account (30-75311), October-December, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - Investment Account (30-75311), January-May, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - Investment Account (30-75311), January-May, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - Portfolios, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 162)
  - Portfolios, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 163)
  - Portfolios, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 164)
  - Portfolios, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 165)
  - Portfolios, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - Portfolios, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - Portfolios, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 168)
  - Securities Purchased, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 169)
  - Securities Sold, 1977-1981 (Box 22, Folder 170)
  - Security Portfolio - Permanent Record, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 171)
  - Special Account, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 172)
- Fiscal, 1981-1982; 3
  - Dissemination Program, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 173)
  - Review of Commonwealth Fund Activities, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 174)
- Taxes, 4
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 175)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 176)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 179)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 180)
  - Federal Form 990, 1940-1968 (Box 23, Folder 181)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 185)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - Federal Form 990, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 187)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 191)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 192)
  - Federal Form 990, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - Federal Form 990, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 194)
  - Federal Form 990, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 195)
  - Federal Form 990, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 196)
  - Federal Form 990, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 197)
  - Federal Forms 1096 and 1099, 1956-1969 (Box 26, Folder 198)
  - Federal Withholding, 1919-1947 (Box 26, Folder 199)
  - Federal Withholding, 1919-1947 (Box 26, Folder 200)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 201)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 202)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 203)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 204)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 205)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 206)
  - Federal Withholding, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 207)
  - Federal Withholding, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 208)
  - Federal Withholding, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 209)
  - Federal Withholding, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 210)
  - Federal Withholding, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 211)
  - Federal Withholding, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 212)
  - New York City Tax, 1966-1972 (Box 28, Folder 213)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 1), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 214)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 215)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 216)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 217)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 218)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 219)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 220)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 221)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 222)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 224)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 225)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 226)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 227)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 228)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 229)
  - New York State - Annual Report to the Attorney General (NYCF 2), 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 230)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1919-1936 (Box 30, Folder 231)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1919-1936 (Box 30, Folder 232)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1919-1936 (Box 30, Folder 233)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 234)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 235)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 236)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 237)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 238)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 239)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1953-1972 (Box 32, Folder 240)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1953-1972 (Box 32, Folder 241)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1953-1972 (Box 32, Folder 242)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1953-1972 (Box 32, Folder 243)
  - New York State - Income Tax, 1953-1972 (Box 32, Folder 244)